Guide to the Western Film Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Western film collection
1911-2006
WA MSS S-2730
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
79.19
(107 boxes) + 5 broadsides
The Western Film Collection consists of press kits, pressbooks, posters, photographs, souvenir programs and other materials that were distributed by film producers to movie theater operators to promote their films. The Western films represented in this collection are Western genre films, films set in the trans-Mississippi West, and/or films with Western characters. Press kits typically include advertisements prepared for submission to newspapers and magazines; black-and-white photographs of scenes from the films with credit information; printed booklets called pressbooks containing information about the film, actors, and other personnel; and posters for lobby display. Early press kits were called "campaign kits." While the majority of press kits included in the collection consist of foldered printed material, there are several examples of electronic press kits on compact disc. The Buddy Holly Story pressbook contains a "flexi disc" recording bound in.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from various sources, 1987-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 50 (sound recording): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 60 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Scope and Contents
The Western Film Collection consists of press kits, pressbooks, posters, photographs, souvenir programs and other materials that were distributed by film producers to movie theater operators to promote their films. The Western films represented in this collection are Western genre films, films set in the trans-Mississippi West, and/or films with Western-type characters. Press kits typically include advertisements prepared for submission to newspapers and magazines; black-and-white photographs of scenes from the films with credit information; printed booklets called pressbooks containing information about the film, actors, and other personnel; and posters for lobby display. Early press kits were called campaign kits. While the majority of press kits included in the collection consist of foldered printed material, there are several examples of electronic press kits on compact disk.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in eleven groupings: I. September 1987 Acquisition, 1940-1979. II. July 2006 Acquistion, 1916-1982. III. June 2010 Acquisition, undated. IV. November 2010 Acquisition, 1932-1934. V. October 2011 Acquisition, 1958-2001. VI. January 2012 Acquisition, 1970-2007. VII. June 2012 Acquistion, 1936-1941. VIII. July 2012 Acquisition, 1936-1941. IX. September 2012 Acquisition, 1949-1950. X. December 2012 Acquisition, 1911-2005. XI. July 2013 Acquisition, 1916-1981.
Motion pictures -- Production and direction; Western films; Born digital; Film posters; Audiovisual materials
- September 1987 Acquisition, 1938-1979; 1.67; (20 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Consists of press kits, pressbooks, posters, and other promotional material.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Walter McClintock Memorial Fund, 1987.
  - Annotated listing of titles, undated (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Ace High, 1968 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - The Alamo, 1960 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Alvarez Kelly, 1966 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Any Gun Can Play, 1967 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Apache / Vera Cruz, 1954 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Apache Drums, 1951 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Apache Territory, 1958 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Apache Uprising, 1965 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - The Appaloosa, 1966 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Arena, 1953 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Backtrack, 1969 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Bad Company, 1972 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Bad Man's River, 1972 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Badlands, 1974 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - The Badlanders, 1958 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Ballad of a Gunfighter, circa 1965 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - The Ballad of Cable Hogue, 1970; 2 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - The Ballad of Josie, 1967 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Bandolero!, 1968 (Box 1 (Oversize))
  - Barquero, 1970 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Les Belles Rouquines, undated (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - The Big Gundown, 1968 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - A Big Hand for the Little Lady, 1966 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Billy Jack, 1971 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Billy Two Hats, 1974 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Black Rodeo, undated (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Bite the Bullet, 1975 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Blindman, 1972 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Blood on the Arrow, 1964 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Blue, 1967 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Boot Hill, 1969; 2 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - The Broken Land, 1961 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - The Broken Star, 1956 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - The Brute and the Beast, 1968 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Buck and the Preacher, 1972 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Buckskin, 1968 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - The Buddy Holly Story, 1978 (Box 2 (Oversize))
  - Bugles in the Afternoon, 1952 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid, 1969 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - California, 1963 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - The Canadians, 1961 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Cannon for Cordoba, 1970 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Captain Apache, 1971 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - The Carpet Baggers / Nevada Smith, 1964, 1965 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - The Castaway Cowboy / The Absent-Minded Professor, 1961 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Cat Ballou, 1965 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Cattle King, 1963; 2 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Charley-One-Eye, 1972 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Charge at Feather River, 1953 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Charley Varrick, 1973 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Chato's Land, 1972 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Cheyenne Autumn, 1965; 2 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - The Cheyenne Social Club, 1970 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Chisum, 1970 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Chuka, 1967 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Cimarron, 1960; 2 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Contre les Daltons [Jesse James vs. The Daltons], 1954 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Convict Stage, 1965; 2 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Coogan's Bluff, 1968 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - The Cowboys, 1972 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Cry Blood Apache, 1970 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - The Culpepper Cattle Co., 1972 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Daniel Boone - Frontier Trail Rider, 1966 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Day of Anger, 1969 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Day of the Evil Gun, 1968 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - The Deadly Trackers, 1973 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Deadwood '76, circa 1965 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Deaf Smith and Johnny Ears, 1973 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Death of a Gunfighter, 1969 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Death Rides a Horse, 1968; 5 (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - The Deserter, 1970 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - The Desperados, 1969 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - The Desperados are in Town, 1956 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Dirty Little Billy, 1972 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Dirty Outlaws, 1971 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - A Distant Trumpet, 1964 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Doc, 1971; 2 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Duck, You Sucker, 1972 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Duel at Diablo, 1966 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Duel in the Sun, 1940; 2 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - El Condor, 1970 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - El Dorado, 1966 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - The Emigrants, 1973 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Escape from Bed Rock, 1955 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Face to the Wind, 1974 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Fair Play, circa 1965 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Fancy Pants, 1950 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - The Far Country / Saskatchewan, 1955, 1954 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - The Fastest Guitar Alive, 1968 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Father Jack-Leg, circa 1970 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Find a Place to Die, circa 1968 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Finger on the Trigger, 1965 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Firecreek, 1967; 2 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - A Fistful of Dollars, 1964 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Fistful of Dollars / For a Few Dollars More, 1964, 1965 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Five Bloody Graves [also known as Gun Riders], 1970 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Five Card Stud, 1968 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Five Guns to Tombstone, 1961 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Flap, 1970 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - For a Few Dollars More, 1965 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Fort Ti, 1953 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Fort Dodds, 1950 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Fort Vengeance, 1953 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Fort Yuma, 1955 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Forty Guns to Apache Pass, 1966 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Frontier Gun, 1958; 2 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Frontier Hellcat, 1966 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Frontier Uprising, 1961 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Gallant Rebel, 1961 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Gambler Wore a Gun, 1961 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Gatling Gun, 1972 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Geronimo!, 1962 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Giant, 1956 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Girl of the Golden West, 1938 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Glory Guys, 1965 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - God Forgives, I Don't, 1969 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Good Guys and The Bad Guys, 1969 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly, 1967 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Great American Cowboy, 1974 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Great Bank Robbery, 1969 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Great Day in the Morning, 1956 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Great Northfield Minnesota Raid, 1972; 2 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Gun Brothers, 1956 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Gun for a Coward, 1956 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - The Gun Hawk, 1963 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Gun Street, 1961 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Gunfight at Comanche Creek, 1964 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Gunfight at the O.K. Corral / Last Train from Gun Hill, 1957, 1959 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Gunfight in Abilene, 1966 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Gunfighters of Casa Grande, 1965; 2 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Gunpoint, 1965 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Guns at Batasi / Apache Rifles, 1964; 2 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Guns of the Magnificent Seven, 1969 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Guns of the Timberland, 1960 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Hallelujah Trail, 1965 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Hang Your Hat on the Wind, 1969 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Hannie Caulder, 1971 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Hatari! / The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance, 1962 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Hatari! / Hud, undated (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - He Rides Tall, 1963 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Heaven with a Gun, 1969 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Hell Bent for Leather, 1960 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - The Hell Bent Kid, 1958 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Heller in Pink Tights, 1960 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - The Hellions, 1967; 2 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - High Plains Drifter, 1973 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - The Hills Run Red, 1967 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Hostile Guns, 1966 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Hot Spur, 1969 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Hour of the Gun, 1967 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - How The West Was Won, 1963 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - The Hunting Party, 1971 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Incident at Phantom Hill, 1965 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - The Incredible Journey, 1963 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - The Indian Fighter, 1955 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Invitation to a Gunfighter, 1964 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - J.W. Coop, 1972 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - The Jayhawkers, 1959 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Jeremiah Johnson, 1972; 3 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Johnny Reno, 1965 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Johnny Yuma, 1966 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Jory, 1972; 2 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Journey Through Rosebud, 1972 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Journey to Shiloh, 1968 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Kentucky Rifle, 1956 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Kid Blue, 1973 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Kid Rodelo, 1966; 2 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - King Solomon's Mines / The Naked Spur, 1950, 1953 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Kiss of Fire, 1955 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Last Challenge, 1967 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Last Command, 1955 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Last Hard Men, 1976 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Last of the Renegades, 1966 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Last Picture Show, 1971; 2 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Last Rebel!, 1960 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Last Sunset, 1961; 2 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - The Lawless Breed / To Hell and Back, 1952, 1955 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Lawman, 1971 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - The Legend of Frenchie King, 1971 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - The Legend of Lobo, 1962 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Lemonade Joe, 1966 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - The Life and Times of Judge Roy Bean, 1972; 3 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Little Big Man, 1971; 3 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Little Fauss & Big Halsy, 1970 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - The Long Rope, 1960 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Lovin' Molly, 1974; 2 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Macho Callahan, 1970 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Mackenna's Gold, 1969 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - The Magnificent Seven / The Horse Soldiers, 1960, 1959 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - The Magnificent Seven Ride, 1972 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Mail Order Bride, 1964 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Major Dundee, 1965 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - A Man Called Gannon, 1969 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - A Man Called Horse, 1970 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The Man Called Noon, 1973 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - A Man Called Sledge, 1971 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The Man from Button Willow, 1965 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The Man from Galveston, 1963 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Man from God's Country, 1950 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The Man from Nowhere, 1968; 2 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Man of the East, 1974 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing, 1973 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Many Rivers to Cross, 1955 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Massacre, 1956 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - McCabe and Mrs. Miller, 1971 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The McMasters, 1970 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - The Mercenary, 1970 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Minnesota Clay, 1965 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die, 1967 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Monte Walsh, 1970 (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Moonlighter, 1953; 2 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Moon Zero Two, 1970 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - More Dead Than Alive, 1969; 2 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Mr. Exhibitor, undated (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - My Name Is Nobody, 1973 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Navajo Joe, 1967 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Ned Kelly, 1970 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Nevada Smith, 1965 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - The New Land, 1973; 3 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - The Night of the Grizzly, 1965 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Once Upon a Time in the West, 1968 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - One-Eyed Jacks, 1959 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - One More Train to Rob, 1970 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Oregon Passage, 1958 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Paint Your Wagon, 1959 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Pancho Villa, 1972 (Box 13 (Oversize))
  - Pat Garrett and Billy The Kid, 1973 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Payment in Blood, 1968 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Peacemaker, 1956 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Pillars of the Sky, 1956 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Pistol for Ringo, 1966 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Plainsman, 1966; 2 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Pocket Money, 1972 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Posse from Hell, 1961 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Preacherman, circa 1973 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Professionals, 1966 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Proud and Damned, 1973 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Purple Hills, 1961 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Quantez, 1957 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Quick Gun, 1964 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Quincannon, Frontier Scout, 1956 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Raiders, 1963 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Rage, 1972 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Rare Breed, 1965 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - The Rawhide Trail, 1958 (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die, 1974 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Redheads from Seattle, 1953; 2 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Red Tomahawk, 1966 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - The Reivers / A Man Called Horse, 1969, 1970 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Requiem for a Gunfighter, 1965 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Return of Sabata, 1972; 2 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Return of the Seven, 1966 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - The Revengers, 1972; 2 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - The Reward, 1965 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - The Ride to Hangman's Tree, 1967 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Riding Tall, 1979 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Rough Night in Jericho, 1967 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - The Rounders, 1965 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Running Wild, 1973 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Sabata, 1970 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - The Saga of Hemp Brown, 1958 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Sam Whiskey, 1969 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Santee, 1973 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - The Savage Guns, 1962; 2 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Savage Pampas, 1966 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Savage Sam, 1963 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Seven Brides for Seven Brothers / Father of the Bride, 1954, 1950 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Seventh Cavalry, 1956 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Shadow of the Hawk, 1976 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Shakiest Gun in Town, 1968 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Shalako, 1968 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Shoot Out, 1971; 2 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - The Shooting, 1967 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Showdown, 1973 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Sierra Stranger, undated (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - The Singer Not the Song, 1962; 2 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Sitting Bull, 1954; 2 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Six Black Horses, 1962 (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Skin Game, 1971 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Smith!, 1960 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Smoky, 1966 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Soldier Blue, 1970 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Something Big, 1971 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Son of a Gunfighter, 1966 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - The Sons of Katie Elder, 1965 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - The Soul of Nigger Charley, 1973 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Soul Soldier, 1971; 2 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - The Spikes Gang, 1974 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Stage to Thunderrock, 1963 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Stagecoach to Dancers' Rock, 1962 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Stranger on Horseback, 1955 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - The Stranger Wore a Gun, 1954 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Sunscorched, 1966 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Support Your Local Gunfighter, 1971 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Sweet Georgia, circa 1965 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Taggart, 1964 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - The Tall Women, 1966 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Taza, Son of Cochise, 1954 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Ten Who Dared, 1960 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Texas Across the River, 1966 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - The Texican, 1966 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - There Was a Crooked Man, 1970 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - They Call Me Trinity, 1971 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Thirteen Fighting Men, 1960 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - This Savage Land, 1969 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Thomasine and Bushrod, 1974 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Three Guns for Texas, 1968 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Thunder at the Border, 1967 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Today We Kill...Tomorrow We Die, circa 1970 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Tomahawk Trail, 1957 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Tonka, 1958; 2 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - The Train Robbers, 1973 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - The Trial of Billy Jack, 1974 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Trigger Happy [formerly known as The Deadly Companions] / The Checkered Flag, 1961, 1962 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Trinity Is Still My Name, 1972; 3 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Two Mules for Sister Sara, 1970 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - The Ugly Ones, 1968 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Ulzana's Raid, 1972 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - The Unsinkable Molly Brown, 1964 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Untamed Frontier, 1952 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Valdez Is Coming, 1971 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Vera Cruz / Apache, 1954 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Villa!, 1958 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Villa Rides!, 1968 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Waco, 1966 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Walk Like a Dragon, 1960 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Walk Tall, 1960 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - War Party, 1964 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - The Way West, 1967 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Welcome to Hard Times, 1967 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Westward Ho, the Wagons, 1957 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - When the Legends Die, 1972 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Where the Red Fern Grows, 1974 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - Wings of the Hawk, 1953; 3 (Box 19 (Oversize))
  - The White Dawn, 1974 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - The Wild Bunch, 1969 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - The Wild Westerners, 1962; 2 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Will Penny, 1967 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - The Wrath of God, 1972 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Young Billy Young, 1969 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Young Fury, 1964 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Young Guns of Texas, 1962 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Young Jesse James, 1960 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Zachariah, 1971 (Box 20 (Oversize))
  - Zandy's Bride, 1974 (Box 20 (Oversize))
- July 2006 Acquisition, 1916-1982; 2.33; (19 boxes)
  Consists of 414 pressbooks and promotional flyers.
  Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2006.
  - 100 Rifles, 1969 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - 3 Desperate Men, 1951 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The 5-Man Army, 1970 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - 7th Cavalry, 1956 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Adios Sabata, 1971 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Adventures of Bullwhip Griffin, 1967 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Adventures of Frank and Jesse James, 1948, 1956 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Al Jennings of Oklahoma, 1951, 1957 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Americano, 1955 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Annie Get Your Gun, circa 1960 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Apache Ambush, 1955 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Apple Dumpling Gang, 1975 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Arena, 1953 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Arizona Bushwhackers, 1967 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Badlands of Montana, 1957 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Badman's Country, 1958 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Baron of Arizona, 1950 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Bears and I, 1974 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1982 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Beyond the Purple Hills, 1956 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Big Country, 1958 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Big Land, circa 1960 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Billy the Kid, 1955 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Black Arrow, 1954 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Black Dakotas, 1954 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Black Spurs, 1964 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Blackjack Ketchum, Desperado, 1956 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - The Blazing Forest, 1952 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Blazing Saddles, 1974 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Bless the Beasts and Children, 1971 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Blood on the Moon, 1957 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Boom Town, 1956 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Borderline, 1980 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Bound for Glory, 1977 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - The Bounty Hunter, 1954 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - The Bounty Killer, 1965 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - The Boy and the Eagle, 1967 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Boys' Ranch, 1946 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - The Bravados, 1958 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Breakheart Pass, 1976 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Brewster McCloud, 1970 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Brighty of the Grand Canyon, 1967 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Bronco Billy, 1980 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Bronco Buster, 1952 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Buckskin Frontier, 1943 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - The Buckskin Lady, 1957 (Box 22 (Oversize))
  - Buffalo Bill and the Indians or Sitting Bull's History Lesson, 1976 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Bullet for a Badman, 1964 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Bullitt, 1968, 1969 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Cahill, 1972 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - California Passage, 1950 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Call of the Wild, 1953 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Cast a Long Shadow, 1959 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - The Cat, 1966 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Catlow, 1971 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Cattle King, 1963 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Charlie, the Lonesome Cougar, 1967 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - The Chase, 1966 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Chinatown, 1974 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Chino, 1973 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - The Cockeyed Cowboys of Calico County, 1970 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Colorado, circa 1960 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Colt, 1950 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Comanche Station, 1960 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - The Comancheros, 1961 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Comes a Horseman, 1978 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Copper Canyon, 1950 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - The Country That God Forgot, 1916 (Box 23 (Oversize))
  - Cowboy, 1958 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - The Crimson Trail, 1952 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Dangers of the Canadian Mounted, 1956 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Davy Crockett / Indian Scout, 1950 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Day of Fury, 1956 (Box 24 (Oversize))